Robert J. Obernier

robertjobernier@gmail.com ● 110 Inverness Dr., Bluffton, SC ● (203) 641-3458 LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/robert-obernier-700b36269/

I am a full stack web developer with a background in computer diagnostics and repair having worked at a computer refurbishing company as well as a general tech repair company. I have earned a certificate in Full Stack Web Development from the University of Connecticut Coding Boot Camp as well a certificate in Web Development and Design from Norwalk Community College while also completing over 50 credits. I have superior time management and organizational skills and am passionate about delivering a superior experience for customers. I am able to take the lead on projects, achieve stated goals, and meet deadlines while working either in a team environment or individually.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, PL/SQL, NoSQL, GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Express, React, Node.js, Handlebars, jQuery, Bootstrap, PHP, Java
- Able to create and maintain websites using the M.E.R.N stack, and with experience in Php, Java, and Oracle PL/SQL
- Proficient with Windows, Microsoft Office and Photoshop
- Capable of using Linux and Ubuntu servers

EDUCATION

University of Connecticut Coding Bootcamp, Online — Certificate in Full Stack Web Development

September 2022 - March 2023

Norwalk Community College, Norwalk, CT — Web development and Design Certificate

August 2018 - May 2021

Norwalk Community College, Norwalk, CT — Associates Degree in Computer Science (incomplete)

August 2015 - Current

Completed over 50 credits including Database Development, Web Development, Java, and Php

WORK EXPERIENCE

uBreakiFix by Asurion, Stamford, CT — Remote/In store Technician March 2022 - July 2022

- Phone repairs including Apple, Samsung and Google
- On site phone repairs, as well as in store
- Work in store on all device types (laptops, desktops, phones, consoles, televisions) while providing excellent customer service

203 Trading LLC, Norwalk, CT — Computer Repair Technician/Ebay Sales January 2020 - March 2022

- Repair computers and prepare them for sale
- Diagnose and fix a wide variety of cosmetic and internal issues
- Expert with Dell, HP, Lenovo, and Fujitsu
- Expert with Microsoft Excel
- Sales on Ebay
- Customer Service

Crystalize Online, Ridgefield, CT — General Worker

2011 - 2013

- Create materials for the company website, including editing and processing images using Adobe Photoshop
- Design and execute online promotions for the company
- Assist with preparing and packing orders for online customers, ensuring 100% accuracy